[{"answer": "No, not as a --", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "If you had been there when it was happening and you saw team after team doing the same thing, do you have any power to actually do something?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm on reconstructed on the subject.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "What is your view about that?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Personally, no.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Should they be?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Yes, you're right.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Wouldn't that -- wouldn't that a one-hit, do more effective work with this than what's going on at the moment?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the lovely thing about the games in the U.K. is we've had the big -- you know, we've had the national pop (ph) game.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Is he?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Well, you have to say that winning 19 medals or whatever he managed last night makes him certainly the most successful and prolific medal winner.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Who do you think is?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I'm from track and field.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Well, modesty probably prohibits me.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Who would it be?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "For snuffing you out that time?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Surely.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "Is there a feeling that if she was an American or a British swimmer, we wouldn't even be debating it?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "Yes, it is one of the top trending topics, especially in the micro blogging sites here.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "That they are now prepared to play by the rules of the Olympic Games?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "I know.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Why is that?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I love to see, you know, incredible performances.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "How exciting has it's been for you?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Have you come through all the traumas and dramas of what went on?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "The mere fact that both of you look so fit, and healthy and well, and happy is all you need to see, isn't it?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "It's not quite as many.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "ORGAN: Even now, do you still have to take a huge amount of pills a day?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm not real political, you know, but I know what's right.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Were you angered when the Chic-fil-A boss said what he said?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Never mind the views about same-sex marriage, right?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "You know, I am so thankful that I was in a sport that we didn't have that really as an issue.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Where are you on all of this?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "When you went back and dived again and you came back up, and your head bounced up through the water, what was going through your mind?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, going through something like that, OK, I hit my head on the board.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "The first thing you thought?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "Greg, it's been a real pleasure to see you.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Well, I look at it differently.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Who would be first choice?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I looked at it in a different way.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "Did you ever in your era come up against anybody who you thought you possibly couldn't beat?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "What's sad about it is that it's never going to end.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Are we better off today than we were when Ben Johnson got caught?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "Oh my goodness, you can't top --", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "Of all the great moments you've had, what was the best for you?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, because it was the first one, you know.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "The Olympics are unique.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Is there anything quite like the Olympics?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Did you ever have that in your time?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 489, "question": "When you were competing at your very best for America and Ronald Reagan was president, did you ever imagine in your lifetime that you would have an African-American president?", "qSentId": 488}, {"answer": "I don't think we became more racist, but I think people woke up the next day and said wait, wait, what happened; let's go back to the old times.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Is it easier or harder to be a black man or woman in America these days?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "To win is something that's unimaginable.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What does it mean A, to compete for your country, for America, and B, to win?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "You sympathize with them?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "It was the way that I always ran since I was a kid.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "It was a natural thing?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a fan of his speed, that's for sure.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Are you a fan of his style?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I think he's had some trouble this year.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "He's been saving himself for the big one?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "I think it does give him an advantage.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "You think it gives him an advantage?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "You can't do that, though.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "I think he probably has earned that advantage, hasn't he?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "No, he's not.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Do you think he might?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "It will be.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "Wouldn't it be an amazing moment for the Olympics?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "OHNSON: The sprints are typically where we have always dominated.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Where are you looking for big American achievement before the end of the games?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "I wouldn't call it running.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "You still running?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "Thank you very much.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "Do you like being called the mother of gymnastics?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "I feel good.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 700, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 699}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "When you walk around here, do you get a good reaction when people realize it's you?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "ORBUT: Yeah.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 706, "question": "Did you really?", "qSentId": 705}, {"answer": "I felt like I was 17 again.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 708, "question": "It all brought it back to you?", "qSentId": 707}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 717, "question": "Was it all easy?", "qSentId": 716}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 739, "question": "What's the one, if I could relive it for you now, which one would you choose?", "qSentId": 738}, {"answer": "Oh, no.", "docId": "120801pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "Is that always the best?", "qSentId": 741}]